<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?> 
<welcomePage 
  title="InterMajik IDE"
  format="wrap">

<intro>Welcome to InterMajik IDE, brought to you by the Maji team at Pagan Labs. </intro>

<item><b>Intermajik Build: </b> PRODUCTTAG
See the <topic id="/org.openmaji.intermajik/html/release-notes/index.html">Release Notes</topic> for more detail.</item>

<item><b>Documentation</b>
Go straight to the <topic id="/org.openmaji.intermajik/html/index.html">InterMajik Documentation</topic></item>

<item><b>Getting Started</b>
Many InterMajik-specific features can be found in the InterMajik menu, in the top-left. This
includes Login/Logout, Worksheet creation, Bug Reporting and Documentation.

Logging in:
Until you have logged in, you will not be able to use InterMajik.  Use the 
"Login InterMajik" button in the Space Browser or Toolkit to select login.  
To logout, use the "down arrow" menu in the Space Browser, or the "InterMajik" menu.

There are three accounts provided, "system" has global write access, "owner" has limited write access
and "guest" has no write access.

Login:   system      Password:   system99
Login:   owner        Password:   owner99
Login:   guest         Password:   guest99

Creating a worksheet:
Log in as the user "owner".
Switch to the Space Browser view and navigate to '/user/owner/'.  Right click on the "owner" category and select 'Add Worksheet'. 
Enter a name for the new worksheet.  The new worksheet will automatically open in the Kinetic Editor.

Creating Meems:
Meems can be dragged from the Toolkit and dropped in a worksheet.
You can also use the tool palette on the left side of the Kinetic Editor to create new Meems, then add wedges to these meems dragged from the Toolkit.
Use the connection tool (or SHIFT-mouse1) to create dependencies.

Adding a Wedge:
To add a wedge to a meem, you need to change it's life cycle state from ready to loaded.
To do this, use the life cycle state icon on the top right of the meem (in it's detailed view).
You can then drag a wedge from the Toolkit onto the meem. Then use the lifecycle icon to make
the meem "ready" again.

Revisiting a worksheet:
To re-open the worksheet, double click on it in the Space Browser.
</item>
</welcomePage>
